<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on Marius Kimmina</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on Marius Kimmina</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 14:10:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox Feline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/feline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/feline/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction The first hard box that I have ever pwned, so lets dive right into it. This box involved a java deserialization attack to first get an inital foothold, once we are on it we use a known exploit in saltstack to become root of docker container, now you might wonder: Why would we want to become root of a docker-container?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox Obscurity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/obscurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/obscurity/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction Yet another HackTheBox Box, this time it was all about obscure hidden stuff and reversing some custom crypto Definitely one of the more ctf-like boxes as this is (probably, you never know) not something you would encounter in a real-world pentest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox OpenAdmin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/openadmin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/openadmin/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction The first HackTheBox Maschine I ever owned, featuring OpenNetAmin and typical admin mistakes 0x1 getting a Foothold&#xA;Like most people probably do I started of the box with an nmap scan which returned the following result:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox Postman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/postman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/postman/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction My first post on a HTB machine and the second Box I managed to own (the first one is yet to retire so there will also be writeup for that) featuring redis and webmin.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
