<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Buffer Overflow on Marius Kimmina</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/buffer-overflow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Buffer Overflow on Marius Kimmina</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 14:10:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/buffer-overflow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Stack-Five</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix5/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction For a full introduction to this series and setup description please look at the first post (Phoenix Stack-Zero and One). This level aims to introduce its participants to the concept of shell-code, thus allowing us to execute code that was not originally part of the program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Stack-Four</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix4/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction For a full introduction to this series and setup description please look at the first post (Phoenix Stack-Zero and One). In the last level of this series we had to overwrite a function pointer to execute a Function that would otherwise never get executed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Stack-Three</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix3/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction For a full introduction to this series and setup description please look at the first post (Phoenix Stack-Zero and One). In this level we have to use yet another buffer-overflow change the Function-pointer to call a specific function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Stack-Two</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix2/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction For a full introduction to this series and setup description please look at the first post (Phoenix Stack-Zero and One). In this level we have to mess with environment variables and unprintable ascii characters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Stack-Zero and One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix1/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction Phoenix is an entry level IT-Security challenge hosted at https://exploit.education/. It consists of multiple levels introducing participants to the concepts of binary exploitation as well as some network-security fundamentals in later levels.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
