<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marius Kimmina</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Marius Kimmina</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 14:10:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ultralearning by Scott H. Young</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/summaries/ultralearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/summaries/ultralearning/</guid>
      <description>In this book the author has analyzed successfull learning projects that seem either extreme or outright impossible such as:&#xA;The entire MIT Computer science undergrad curriculum in one year Learning a foreign langauge in 3 months Develop a video game all by yourself (stardew valley) and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Automated TLS Certificates in CoreDNS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/automated_certs_coredns/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/automated_certs_coredns/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever had to setup DNS over TLS for your Domain Nameserver?&#xA;As a Developer who normally doesn&amp;rsquo;t put too much thought into infrastructure related topics, that can be a daunting task.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox Feline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/feline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/feline/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction The first hard box that I have ever pwned, so lets dive right into it. This box involved a java deserialization attack to first get an inital foothold, once we are on it we use a known exploit in saltstack to become root of docker container, now you might wonder: Why would we want to become root of a docker-container?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox Sauna</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/sauna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/sauna/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction Welcome to another HackTheBox writeup, in this one we have to enumerate users, make heavy use of impacket scripts to kerberoast one of the users and we utilize winpeas to escalate our privileges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CAP Theorem</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/til/2023-09-17-captheorem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/til/2023-09-17-captheorem/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox ServMon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/servmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/servmon/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction Yet another Windows box. In this one we use anonymous ftp access to find out about the existens of some internal files and then abuse a path traversal vulnerability to get hold of these files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox Resolute</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/resolute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/resolute/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction This was a medium Windows Box, featuring rpcclient, default Passwords and a dll injection. This one took me quite a bit of time as I am not that used to working with Windows maschines and I learned a lot from this one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox Obscurity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/obscurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/obscurity/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction Yet another HackTheBox Box, this time it was all about obscure hidden stuff and reversing some custom crypto Definitely one of the more ctf-like boxes as this is (probably, you never know) not something you would encounter in a real-world pentest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox OpenAdmin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/openadmin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/openadmin/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction The first HackTheBox Maschine I ever owned, featuring OpenNetAmin and typical admin mistakes 0x1 getting a Foothold&#xA;Like most people probably do I started of the box with an nmap scan which returned the following result:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox Traverxec</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/traverxec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/traverxec/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction Yet another HTB box and again one of the easier ones. This time we had to exploit a vulnerable nostromo webserver version for command execution and then escalate privileges from there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HackTheBox Postman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/postman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/postman/</guid>
      <description>0x0 Introduction My first post on a HTB machine and the second Box I managed to own (the first one is yet to retire so there will also be writeup for that) featuring redis and webmin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>36C3 Maybe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/36c3maybe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/36c3maybe/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction This Challenge was part of the 36C3 Junior CTF. It was a reverse engeneering challenge with a difficulty rating of medium. You were only given a binary.&#xA;0x1. Something is weird here The first thing I always do for reverse engeneering challenges is to look at the binary with &amp;ldquo;file&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>36C3 Querying</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/36c3querying/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/36c3querying/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction This Challenge was part of the 36C3 Junior CTF. It was a &amp;ldquo;Web&amp;rdquo; challenge with a difficulty rating of &amp;ldquo;Medium&amp;rdquo;, you were given an URL for the live challenge server and also a copy of the server (with a fake flag obv) as a Docker Container to run locally to test your exploits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Stack-Five</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix5/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction For a full introduction to this series and setup description please look at the first post (Phoenix Stack-Zero and One). This level aims to introduce its participants to the concept of shell-code, thus allowing us to execute code that was not originally part of the program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Stack-Four</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix4/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction For a full introduction to this series and setup description please look at the first post (Phoenix Stack-Zero and One). In the last level of this series we had to overwrite a function pointer to execute a Function that would otherwise never get executed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Stack-Three</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix3/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction For a full introduction to this series and setup description please look at the first post (Phoenix Stack-Zero and One). In this level we have to use yet another buffer-overflow change the Function-pointer to call a specific function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Stack-Two</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix2/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction For a full introduction to this series and setup description please look at the first post (Phoenix Stack-Zero and One). In this level we have to mess with environment variables and unprintable ascii characters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Stack-Zero and One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 14:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hacks/phoenix1/</guid>
      <description>0x0. Introduction Phoenix is an entry level IT-Security challenge hosted at https://exploit.education/. It consists of multiple levels introducing participants to the concepts of binary exploitation as well as some network-security fundamentals in later levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey, I&amp;rsquo;m Marius. I work as a Software Engineer and focus on automation, infrastructure and security.&#xA;Officially, my current job title is &amp;ldquo;DevOps Engineer&amp;rdquo;. I am currently working with&#xA;and learning about AWS and Terraform while also coding in Go.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
